Oh. Lucy's free after all, see you.
No, no, no, hey, hey, hey,
you can't leave, we just started.
(Raj:)You're right, I should finish the game.
I take my plus-one long sword...
(Raj:)...stab myself in the face with it.
I'm dead, I've got a date with a girl. Bye.
(Howard:)We'll be fine. Watch.
Ahem. Suddenly, a spectral shape rises from
Koothrappali's bloody corpse and says:
"Don't worry, buddies. Ghost
Raj will help guide you through the forest."
(Howard:)I'm just a tree,
but if I were you, I'd listen to your ghost friend.
(Sheldon:)Go on. Give him your lunch money.
(Raj:)I'm very happy you were able to hang out.
(Lucy:)Me too.
(Raj:)Not that it's up to you to make me happy.
Unless you find neediness sexy...
...in which case you're with
the hottest man on the planet. Heh.